foknewschannel.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy // Current

Current respects your privacy. We recognize the potential of technology to help you communicate with us via our website and through e-mail and we would like to use this technology over time to develop a relationship with you. The privacy policy below details the measures taken by CURRENT TV, LLC ("Current") to protect your privacy in connection with your use of www.current.tv and other sites owned by Current (collectively, "Site"). Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Current Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of this privacy policy or the Terms of Use, please do not provide Current with any information and do not use the Site. Your continued use of the Site after the privacy policy has been modified will signify your acceptance of the changes for information gathered after the date of the change. 

This policy statement discloses our privacy practices including the notification of: 

  * Personally identifiable information ("PII") collected through our Site;
  * Intended usage of this PII;
  * Choices available regarding opt-in/opt-out, data collection, use and distribution of the information;
  * Security measures to protect the loss or misuse of information under Current's control;
  * How to maintain the accuracy of your information.

In general, you may visit our Site and access information while not revealing any individual user information other than Technology Related Information (defined below). If you upload content to this Site, the content will be governed by the Terms of Use and any other terms or conditions on the upload pages. The types of individual user information collected in the registration process may include your name, contact information, other PII and other information volunteered by you. 

Current collects PII when you register with Current, when you visit Current pages and when you deliver communications or content to the Site. Current may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business associates or otherwise. Without limitation, information collected, including PII, may be used by Current for internal research purposes, marketing, promotions and public relations, subject only to the terms of our privacy policy. 

Current will not disclose, transfer, sell or otherwise communicate your PII to any third party, other than Current's parent, subsidiaries and affiliates, and each of (i) their employees or (ii) vendors and contractors operating under confidentiality agreements and subject to Current's privacy policy, unless you give Current permission to do so, except as set forth in this privacy policy. Notwithstanding the foregoing or anything to the contrary, Current may disclose any information you provide if required to do so by law or pursuant to a request by law enforcement or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with the legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Current or third parties; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety or legal rights ("Mandatory Disclosures"). As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or change our name or form of entity, and, depending upon the transaction, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets; provided, however, we will not sell or transfer PII except subject to the terms of our privacy policy. For instance, in the event that Current is acquired by another company, your PII may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. Current will notify you before PII about you becomes subject to a different privacy policy. The collected information may be provided in the aggregate to third parties, including potential business partners and advertisers, but this information is not linked to any PII before it is disclosed unless Current has obtained your consent. 

To help administer our Site and provide a positive experience while visiting our Site, Current does collect technology-related information. "Technology-Related Information" may include, but is not limited to the following: source IP address, domain name, date and time visited and visited pages. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We use cookies for many purposes such as to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests. Current may set and access Current "cookies" on your computer. Current lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Current's cookies. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Current has no control over the information collected from or about you by any third party after you have left the Site. By clicking on links to other websites, advertisers and other third parties, you are leaving the Site. Once you have left the Site, Current does not control the data collection and privacy practices, or other activities, of any third party linked to this Site and Current assumes no liability and is not responsible for any practices of such third party websites. 

Current may consider requests from unrelated third parties to contact you, but we will not give that third party any PII unless Current has obtained your consent. You may give this consent by "opting-in" to having your information shared with third parties when you register. Additionally, Current provides you the opportunity to be sent newsletters and information about programming, promotional events, marketing events and opportunities to participate in research studies. If you would like to exercise your right under the CAN SPAM Act to not receive future e-mail correspondence from us, except with respect to your prior financial transactions or communications, regarding Mandatory Disclosures or as otherwise required by law, you may do so by using a link provided at the bottom of these communications. You can also send us an email at [privacy@current.com](mailto:privacy@current.com) for any opt-out or opt-in purpose. You may review, change or delete any information you submitted to Current by going to the registration page at any time. You must include your name and password, and a description of the information you would like to change. Alternatively, you can send mail to the following postal address: Current TV, LLC, 118 King Street, San Francisco, CA 94107 (Attn: Privacy). 

Current endeavors to ensure the commercially reasonable protection of user's PII. We have implemented security measures to protect PII collected on our Site against loss, misuse or alteration. However, the Internet is an open system and technology and human operators are not infallible. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee that the individual user information you have transmitted, including PII, will not be intercepted by others and/or decrypted or accidentally disclosed. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet, and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

As a user of the Site, please understand that our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we decide to make any material changes, we will post these changes on the Site. If, at any point, we decide to use PII in a manner different than what was stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users of this change by email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. Current will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected unless you agree otherwise. 

A Special Note about Children, Children's Privacy and Our Compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act 

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we are a general audience site and do not intend to collect any PII from children under 13 years of age, unless we believe such collection to be permitted by law. Our Site targets an audience that is over the age of 18 and some content may not be appropriate for all ages. Parental supervision is recommended. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 and believe that he or she has disclosed PII to us, please contact us at [privacy@current.com](mailto:privacy@current.com). Upon request, the parent or guardian of a child under 13 may review and request the deletion of such child's PII, as well as refuse to permit the further collection or use of such PII. 

Still have Questions? If you have any questions, or believe Current is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, you should contact Current's privacy manager by email at [privacy@current.com](mailto:privacy@current.com). Alternatively, you can send mail to the following postal address: Current TV, LLC, 118 King Street, San Francisco, CA 94107 (Attn: Privacy). 

This privacy policy was last changed and posted on our Site on April 4, 2005.
